-Good afternoon!
Good afternoon.
-Where did the car go?
It has happened a bit since last time.
-The time I was here put it together but it doesn't do it anymore.
-The car is completely dismantled.
Yes.
It is easy to mow with.
I didn't need any help I could lift everything myself.
It went pretty fast.
I have built the car myself so I know what order it should be picked down.
What is left to pick down is front and rear wagon.
Then I start with the frame and weld the holes again, put and paint.
After that, the frame should be foiled.
-Who should do the foil?
I do that myself.
I have ordered material.
-Have you done it before?
Yes we often do it on the buses at work.
-Oh okay.
And the engine should be cleaned and painted.
-What is it for color?
It becomes plain silver.
The color will not appear so it becomes something simple.
-Type Matt Silver?
Yes.
-like the covers here?
Yes exactly it will be the same.
I have also prepared the stainless steel exhaust system and suction.
What is located here should be sent on electrolyte polishing.
I don't really know how it goes.
I think they dip it in some kind of acid.
So it corrodes all deposits from welding, etc.
Then some other liquid and last with current and then it becomes a glossy surface.
It will be exciting to see how it will be when it comes back.
That section here ...
... was at the water tank and here it sat double plate.
It was upset so this part is changed.
I have done this reinforcement cross.
So that the frame becomes more rotated.
Now it is a mute frame when all rivets are welded.
There are no rivets left.
The attachments for the leaf suspension are original.
They sit on the outside which is good.
Often on passenger cars, the attachment sat in the middle or on the inside.
Its further out they sit so more stable, the car becomes good.
The rear axle is from a Camaro from 1977 or -78.
I've got hold of the murders brakes from 1953. -hahaha!
It's Bolt On.
From 1929 until 1953, they have not changed anything.
What if it could be the same on today's cars?
I have changed so that the front car is above the leaf suspension instead of below.
It lowers the car almost 10 cm.
Right.
It provides a smooth height front and rear.
This is an original beam that I have redone a bit.
I have raised the beam because the front carriage comes higher up so it does not hit when it springs.
And that it is welded instead of rivets.
Here I have some left to weld.
I haven't accessed before.
Yes you have things to do?
Yes, there are a few weeks left for Easter.
Surely it is two months left for Easter?
Yes something like that.
I would have had anxiety if I knew it was only 2 months left and so much to do.
That's what pepper one.
It is almost as fast to pick it up as apart.
When it is to be picked up, each part must be polished before.
I have gone through it 2-3 times before so there should be no problems.
-What are you grinding this one with?
It is its own invention.
... I have used lying down but then I have to renovate them.
It would have been smooth with two new ones so I don't have to do that much.
I realized that you had no floor in the cab last.
No, I have made a template.
Ah a woodwall, huh?
Yes this template fits both on the right and left side.
Easy to grind and cut out a new one.
So I have the whole floor.
Will it be in sheet metal then or?
No, it actually becomes such a 10 mm wooden board.
There will be good sound insulation.
Plate is happy to be shameful.
Otherwise it is not so much more.
A little putty and painting on the frame.
All that job I will do down here.
It's not the weather to take a frame outdoors now.
It is better to stay here and do it yourself.
It should not be painted it will be brush painted.
The frame should be ground down so it becomes smooth and then foil.
Most of it will happen down here in the garage.